Rubin, Harold; Papers apap032
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Harold Rubin Papers
1958-2004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap032
7.0 cubic ft.
Subject files largely consisting of retained records of local organizations dedicated to preserving Albany, New York historic neighborhoods and architecture as well as the Pine Bush.
Biographical History
Harold Rubin was born in the Bronx and began his civil service career with New York State in 1950 as a statistician with the Public Service Commission. He joined the Department of Commerce in 1953 as an economist and the division of the Budget in 1956 as a research analyst, where he held a variety of positions until he retired in 1989 as a chief budget examiner. Rubin has a B.S.S. from the City College of New York and a M.P.A. and a Ph.D. from Syracuse University. A prominent Albany neighborhood activist since the 1960s, he is also known for his participation in a 1978 lawsuit which stopped Governor Carey's attempt to disclose the outside income of top level bureaucrats.
As a community leader, Rubin has chaired the Council of Albany Neighborhood Associations (CANA) from its inception in 1976 to May 1996. While playing a significant role advocating neighborhood concerns throughout the City of Albany, Rubin has also been active in the Center Square Neighborhood Association, his residence since 1964. He has also been an active member of the Coalition for Effective Code Enforcement, the Neighborhood Resource Center, and Friends of Albany Public Library. Among the causes that Rubin has fought for are tenants rights and the preservation and restoration of historic buildings and areas in Albany [Information on Harold Rubin's career from Kyle Hughes, "Albany's Gadfly Ends State Career", Albany Times Union, 3 May 1989; Karen Roach, "Neighborhood Group Turns 20", The Daily Gazette, 28 January 1996; and from Harold Rubin].
Scope and Contents
The Harold Rubin Papers consist for the most part of files Rubin kept as a neighborhood activist interested in historic preservation and neighborhood renewal in Albany, New York between 1964 and 2002. To a lesser degree they document Rubin's legal struggles with the administration of New York State Governor Hugh Carey over Carey's 1978 attempt to force New York State civil servants to disclose outside sources of income, and his interest in Governor Mario M. Cuomo's attempt to withhold salary increases for civil servants.
Rubin chaired the Council of Albany Neighborhood Associations (CANA) from May 1976 to May 1996. CANA is the coordinating body for Albany neighborhood associations. Rubin has also been involved with the Neighborhood Resources Center, the Center Square Association (his neighborhood), and the Capitol Hill Architectural Review Commission. His files on these organizations contained correspondence, minutes, news clippings on the organizations and issues they were interested in, organizational newsletters, and reports. His files also contain extensive correspondence with other Albany neighborhood organizations such as Hudson/Park Neighborhood Association and Pine Hills Neighborhood Association. The files included correspondence with Albany organizations interested in urban renewal and historic preservation including the Capitol Hill Improvement Corporation, the Capitol Housing Rehabilitation Corporation, the Historic Albany Foundation, Historic Resources Commission (1988), Historic Sites Commission, Albany Industrial Development Agency, Mayor Corning Memorial Committee (1984), and St. Joseph Housing Corporation (1983).
Rubin's files also contain correspondence with New York City and New York State organizations interested in historic preservation including the Brownstone Revival Committee, New York State Council on Architecture, and Preservation League of New York State; and national correspondence with and information on the Alliance for Neighborhood Government and Neighborhood Preservation. There is also a small general Clippings/Miscellaneous File on Albany issues of concern to Rubin.
The files are organized into four series: Albany Community Subject Files, 1964-1989; a State Employment Subject File, 1975-1977; a Neighborhood Associations File which contains sub-series on the following organizations: Council of Albany Neighborhood Associations (CANA), 1975-2002, Neighborhood Resource Center, 1975-1990, Center Square Association, 1972-1979, Capitol Hill Architectural Review Commission, 1971-1988, Coalition for Effective Code Enforcement, 1974-1977; and a general Clippings/Miscellaneous File, 1972-1980. An inventory of the 2004 accession is also included in the relevant series, but that material has not as of yet been fully arranged and described.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized as follows:
Series 1: Albany Community Subject Files, 1964-1990
Series 2: State Employment File, 1975-1984
Series 3: Neighborhood Associations File, 1972-2002
Sub-series 1: Council of Albany Neighborhood Associations (CANA), 1975-2002
Sub-series 2: The Neighborhood Resources Center, 1975-1992
Sub-series 3: The Center Square Association, 1969-1979
Sub-series 4: The Capitol Hill Architectural Review Commission, 1971-1988
Sub-series 5: The Coalition for Effective Code Enforcement, 1974-1978
Series 4: Clippings/Miscellaneous Files, 1972-1980
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by Harold Rubin on August 1, 1989; October 1, 1989; July 27, 1990; September 13, 2002; and September 8, 2004.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Social Activists and Public Advocates; Neighborhood and Community Associations; Conservation and the Environment; Architecture; Albany, New York; Citizens' associations -- New York (State) -- Albany.; Neighborhood government -- New York (State) -- Albany.; Historic building -- Conservation and restoration -- New York (State) -- Albany.; Rubin, Harold.; Capital Hill Architectural Review Commission.; Center Square Neighborhood Association.; Coalition for Effective Code Enforcement.; Council of Albany Neighborhood Associations.
- Albany Community Subject Files, 1964-1990; 1; 2.7 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  The files contain newspaper clippings, codes, and investigations on a wide range of topics pertaining to urban issues such as housing codes and enforcement, highway construction, parking, preservation and demolition of buildings and historical sites, preservation of the Pine Bush, security, burglary, a 1973 investigation of police enforcement and corruption, taxes, urban community and neighborhood development and preservation, ordinances, and zoning. They contain correspondence with and information on the Hudson/Park and Pine Hills Neighborhood Associations, Albany neighborhood associations, Capitol Hill Improvement Corporation, Capitol Housing Rehabilitation Corporation, the Historic Albany Foundation, Historic Resources Commission (1988), Historic Sites Commission, Albany Industrial Development Agency, Mayor Corning Memorial Committee (1984), and St. Joseph Housing Corporation (1983); and correspondence with and information on the New York City Brownstone Revival Committee, New York State Council on Architecture, and Preservation League of New York State; and national correspondence with and information on Alliance for Neighborhood Government, and Neighborhood Preservation.
  The subject files also contain information on the development and building of the Civic Center, Capitol State Plaza, and South Mall, the preservation and history of such sites as Arbor Hill, Center Square, the Pine Bush specific to the building of Crossgates Mall, Pastures Preservation District (1973), the urban renewal of Ten Broeck Triangle, and Mansion Area, and the 1980-1981 demolition controversy over one of the buildings purchased by the Fort Orange Club to be demolished for parking spaces.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Albany Civic Center, 1985 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Albany City Salary Increases, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Albany Code Enforcement (contains news clippings), 1973-1977 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Albany Code Enforcement, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 5-6)
  - Albany Code Enforcement, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Albany Code Enforcement, 1974-1977 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Albany Code Enforcement: Rev Potter, 1976 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Albany Common Council Procedures, 1980-1986 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Albany Department of Buildings, 1974-1979 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Albany Ethics Commission, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Albany Finances, 1983-1987 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Albany Financial Report, 1980 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Albany Highway Construction, 1983 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Albany Housing, 1980-1985 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 16-17)
  - Albany Parking Permit System, 1974-1979 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Albany Parking Permit System, 1984-1987 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Albany Police Department, Investigation, 1973 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Albany, Preservation/Demolition, 1976-1989 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Albany Prison, 1982 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Albany Security Ordinance, 1980 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Albany Strategic Plan, 1985 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 24-26)
  - Albany Tax Delinquency, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Albany, Taxes, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Alliance for Neighborhood Government, 1976 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Anti Grouper Legislation, 1975-1985 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Arbor Hill, History, Undated (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Brownstone Revival Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Burglary Protection, 1975 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Capital Hill Improvement Corp, 1977-1988 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Capital Housing Rehabilitation Corp, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Capital State Plaza, Undated (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - City Living Series, 1974-1978 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Civil Service Mgt, 1982-1984 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Center Square, 1974 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Coalition for Fair Assessments, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Community Development, 1974-1980 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Community Development, 1974-1977 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Community Development, 1975-1977 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Community Development, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 44-45)
  - Community Development, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Community Development, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 3-4)
  - Community Development, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Community Development, 1983 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Community Development, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Community Development, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Community Development, Central Avenue, 1981 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Fort Orange Club, Demolition, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 10-11)
  - Friends of Albany Public Library, 1972-1990 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Historic Albany Foundation, 1974-1989 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 13-15)
  - Historic Preservation, Clippings, 1971-1975 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Historic Preservation, Periodical, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Historic Resources Commission, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Historic Sites Commission, 1964-1988 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Hudson Park Neighborhood Association, 1973-1988 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Industrial Development Agency, 1980-1984 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Mayor Corning Memorial Committee, 1984 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Mayor's Cup, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Neighborhood Associations, 1970-1980 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Neighborhood Associations, Undated (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Neighborhood Associations, Conventions, 1976-1990 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Neighborhood Preservation, 1976-1980 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - New York State Council on Architecture, 1974-1988 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Pastures Preservation District, 1973 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Pine Bush, 1978 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Pine Hills Neighborhood Association, 1970-1988 (Box 2 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Preservation League, 1976-1987 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Preservation League Newsletters, 1976-1987 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Preservation League, 1977-1987 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Red-lining, 1975-1978 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Retaliatory Eviction Protection, 1978 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Salary Withholding Lawsuit, 1983 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - St. Joseph's Housing Corporation, 1983 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - South Mall Envisions, 1972-1974; 2 folders (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
  - Ten Broeck Triangle, Urban Renewal, 1980 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 9-10)
  - Thomas J. Senchyna Award, 1981-1990 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Urban Development Action Program, 1978-1985 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - University/Community, 1985-1986 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Urban Renewal, Mansion Area, 1908 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Zoning, 1983 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Zoning, 1988 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Zoning, Use Variance, 1984 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Zoning, Definition of Family, 1973-1985 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Zoning, Definition of Family Lawsuits, 1972 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Zoning, Definition of Family Lawsuits, 1973 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Zoning, Definition of Family Lawsuits, 1974-1979 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Zoning Ordinances, 1967; 1978 (Box 3 (1-Albany Community Subject Files), Folder 22)
- State Employment File, 1975-1984; 2; 0.6 cubic ft.
  The files relate primarily to Harold Rubin's opposition to Governor Hugh Carey's attempt (Executive Order #10, #10-1) to impose financial disclosure requirements on civil servants which would have curtained their participation in outside activities. They include a statement by Barbara Zaron, president of the Organization of New York State Management/Confidential Employees, at the Civil Service Merit System Hearing of 1984 and two letters on the issue. Also included are briefs and a memorandum on James T. Evans, M.D. vs. Hugh L. Carey, Governor, concerning the public financial disclosure of civil servants private income records and the briefs on Susan Rapp vs Governor Carey on disclosure of public servants and the the Executive Order overturned by the New York Supreme Court of Appeals in James T. Evans vs. Governor Carey. There are briefs and exhibits on the salary increase withholding lawsuit of 1983, Charles Shattenkirk and Eugene Tashman vs Michael Finnerty, Budget Director of New York State, and Governor Mario Cuomo.
  - Evans, James T. vs. Gov. Carey, 1976 (Box 3 (2-State Employment File), Folder 23)
  - Executive Order #10, 1975-1976 (Box 3 (2-State Employment File), Folder 24)
  - Executive Order 10-1, 1976 (Box 3 (2-State Employment File), Folder 25)
  - Executive Order 10-1, 1976-1977 (Box 3 (2-State Employment File), Folder 26)
  - Rapp, Susan v Gov. Carey, 1976-1977 (Box 3 (2-State Employment File), Folder 27)
  - Rapp, Susan v Gov. Carey, 1977 (Box 3 (2-State Employment File), Folder 28)
  - Supreme Court Briefs, 1977 (Box 4 (2-State Employment File), Folder 1)
  - Supreme Court Briefs, Rapp v Carey, 1977 (Box 4 (2-State Employment File), Folder 2-3)
  - Unprocessed Accession, Undated; 2.9
    SUNY/TIAA, Pension options prior to adoption of TIAA-CREF, Pensions- Vesting, Albany Industrial Project (1996-1997)
- Neighborhood Associations Files, 1972-2002; 3; 2.0 cubic ft.
  The file contains clippings, correspondence, minutes of meetings, newsletters and other publications, reports, records of lawsuits, relating to Harold Rubin's membership in or interest in Albany neighborhood associations and groups involved in urban renewal and revitalization (historic preservation) including: the Capital Hill Architectural Review Commission, the Center Square Association, Council of Albany Neighborhood Associations, the Neighborhood Resource Center. The files are organized into sub-series by association or organization as follows:
  Arranged in sub-series by organization and alphabetically thereunder.
  - Council of Albany Neighborhood Associations (CANA), 1975-2002; 3.1
    CANA is an umbrella organization of active neighborhood groups, and associate group members, involved in such issues as the city budget, mayor's salary increases, Capital Plaza security, Common Council Procedures, Ethics Committee, a proposed "Floor Thru" zoning amendment to authorize multiple dwellings in certain neighborhoods, historic preservation, home occupation, community development, regulating business signs (the Key Bank sign controversy), and other city issues. The Albany city budget files include news clippings, correspondence, testimony before the city council by members of CANA, and city budget's. The files also include CANA minutes and newsletters.
    - Albany Budget, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 4)
    - Albany Budget, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 5)
    - Albany Budget, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 6)
    - Albany Budget, 1978 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 7)
    - Albany Budget, 1979 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 8)
    - Albany Budget, 1980 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 9)
    - Albany Budget, 1981 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 10)
    - Albany Budget, 1982 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 11)
    - Albany Budget, 1983 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 12)
    - Albany Budget, 1984 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 13)
    - Albany Budget, 1985 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 14)
    - Albany Budget, 1986 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 15)
    - Albany Budget, 1987 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 16)
    - Albany Budget, 1988 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 17)
    - Albany Budget, 1989 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 18)
    - Albany Budget, 1990 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 19)
    - Albany Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 20)
    - Albany Budget, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 21)
    - Albany Budget, 1995 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 22)
    - Albany Budget, 1996 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 23)
    - Albany Budget, 1997 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 24)
    - Albany Budget, 1998 (Box 4 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 25)
    - Albany Budget, 1999 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 1)
    - Albany Budget, 2000 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 2)
    - Albany Budget, 2002 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 3)
    - Albany Mayor Salary Increases, 1986 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 4)
    - Capital Plaza Security, 1980 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 5)
    - Common Council Procedures, 1980-1986 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 6)
    - Community Development, 1975-1981 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 7)
    - Ethics Committee, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 8)
    - "Floor Thru" Zoning, 1981-1982 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 9)
    - Historic Preservation Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 10)
    - Home Occupation, 1981-1984 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 11)
    - Key Bank Sign, 1983 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 12)
    - Minutes, 1977; 1995 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 13)
    - Newsletters, 1977 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 14)
    - Public Notices, 1979-1981 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 15)
    - Smith vs. Albany, 1983-1984 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 16)
    - Storage Regulations, 1982 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 17)
    - Tax Assessments, 1987 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 18)
    - Trash Collection Scandal, 1983 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 19)
    - Unprocessed Accession, Undated; 3.1.42
      - Albany Budget, 2001
      - Albany Budget, 2003
      - Albany Budget, 2004
  - The Neighborhood Resources Center, 1975-1992; 3.2
    Contains general correspondence, clippings, committee placements, Director's reports, minutes, publications, and information on annual meetings and the Anti-Crime projects.
    - Annual Meetings, 1976-1989 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 20)
    - Anti-Crime Project, 1978-1979 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 21-23)
    - Anti-Crime Projects, 1979-1983 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 24)
    - Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 25)
    - Committee Placements, 1976-1990 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 26)
    - Director's Report, 1975-1982 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 27)
    - Director's Report, 1983-1989 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 28)
    - General Correspondence, 1975-1982 (Box 5 (3-Neighborhood Associations Files), Folder 29)